好家伙 这可真是个难题啊
Boy, that's a toughie.
你们还有联系?
You still see her?
呃 不是那种联系
Well, no, not socially.
但 你要知道 工作的时候会见到嘛
But, you know, just at work.
你和她一起工作?!
You work with her?!
为什么不告诉我?!
How could you not tell me that?!
在车里的时候我想告诉你来着 但你叫我闭嘴!
I wanted to tell you in the car, but you told me to stop talking!
哦 好吧 所以这都是我的错咯?
Oh, okay. So you're saying this is my fault?
不 当然不是了
No, of course not.
好吧 听着
Okay, look,
与其接着吵架
instead of fighting,
我们还不如把灯关了
why don't we dim the lights,
嗯 把衣服脱了然后一起造个人?
um, get naked and make a baby?
我只不过是想缓和下气氛
I was trying to lighten the mood.
很不容易的 你试试就知道了
It's not easy. You try it.
你好 母亲
Hello, Mother.
Shelly! 我的宝贝最近如何啊?
Shelly! How's my baby doing?
我只想让你知道
I just wanted to let you know
Amy可以从你的夜晚祷告名单里面除去了
that you can remove Amy from your nightly prayers.
除非你愿意帮我祈祷
Unless you're open to praying for
一个蜂窝会扣在她头上
a beehive to fall on her head.
哦 怎么了?
Oh, what's going on?
她和我分手了
She broke up with me.
哦 Shelly
Oh, Shelly.
不 我会没事的
No, I'll be okay.
不过 我觉得我可以
But I think that I'd like
把戒指寄回给您了
to send the ring back to you.
不要太着急
Well, let's not be hasty.
你确定一切都结束了吗?
Are you sure it's over for good?
我是结束了 我受够女人了
It's over for me. I'm done with women.
就像我发誓不吃跳跳糖一样
Like when I swore off Pop Rocks.
他们都是故意伤人的
They both hurt you on purpose.
可以告诉我事情的经过吗?
You want to tell me what happened?
你会说一切都是冥冥之中天注定的吗?
Are you going to say it's all part of God's plan?
很有可能
Good chance.
那算了 谢谢
Then no, thank you.
宝贝啊 先别寄回来
Well, honey, don't send it back yet.
你姐姐已经结婚了 我不想让你哥
Your sister's married, and I'm not letting your brother
把祖传戒指交给他正在交往的贱人
give my grandmother's ring to that whore he's dating.
抹大拉的马利亚（被耶稣拯救的妓女）不也名誉不佳吗?
Wasn't Mary Magdalene a woman of ill repute?
等哪天你那不开窍的哥哥拯救了人类
When your idiot brother redeems mankind,
他想和谁交往都行
he can date whoever he wants.
我知道你现在很伤心 但会好起来的
I know it hurts now, but it's gonna get better.
没错
Yeah.
一切都会好转的
Everything's gonna be okay.
你身上优点多得是
You've got so much to offer.
谢谢你
Thank you.
与你相伴是任何男人的福分
Any man would be lucky to have you.
一点没错
That's true.
我只是希望我做对了事情
I just hope I did the right thing.
那是肯定的
I'm sure you did.